zippytune.com 2015-06-07

# Privacy Policy - ZippyTune - Share Your Tracks.

This Privacy Policy describes the kinds of information that ZippyTune (“we”) may collect about you through our group of websites and others where this Policy appears (the “Sites”), and what we may do with that information. We reserve the right to modify this Policy at any time by posting the updated version here and changing the “version” date above. Therefore, please check this page for updates whenever you visit any of our Sites, and we may also elect to notify our registered users of material changes via e-mail or other means. This Policy does not apply to information that may be collected off-line. 

By visiting or registering at one or more of the Sites, you acknowledge that you have read, understand and agree to be bound by this Policy as it may be amended from time to time, and to our collection, transfer (if applicable), storage and processing of your information in the United States of America. If you do not agree to these terms, please navigate away from the Site and do not register, make any purchases or provide us with any personal information about you. 

**What information do we collect?**

We generally collect two kinds of information through the Site: “personal information” about you which you provide to us, and “non-personal information” about you, your computer and technology, and your use of the Sites, which alone doesn’t identify you personally. 

In order for you to become a registered user, make purchases from, or sell content through our Sites, you will need to provide us with certain personal information, such as your age, name, business name if applicable, e-mail address, street address and telephone number during the registration process. For online purchases or sales, we will also require your credit or debit card number, expiration date, billing address and related details (which may include your social security or other tax ID number) in order to process payments. We may also ask for additional personal information from time to time such as such as gender and income level, in connection with online promotions, contests, giveaways, surveys and other programs, but it’s entirely up to you whether or not to provide that information to participate in those programs. 

We may also collect non-personal information from visitors and registered users of the Sites. We may ask you to provide some of that information yourself, such as your musical preferences, your favorite artists, labels or genres, or your purchasing, listening and concert-going habits. Other technical, geographic and usage data and information we may collect directly, such as your browser type, ISP, operating system, log and Site usage data, IP address, zip code or location, the pages you visit and music or other content that you listen to or access while on the Sites, websites you’ve visited upon entering or leaving the Sites, and if you purchase or sell content through the Sites we will keep track of those purchases and/or sales. Such information may be combined with your personal information. 

If you contact or communicate with us or our representatives by e-mail or through the Sites, or if you post any information on any forums, chat rooms, profile pages, feedback, customer service or other portions of the Sites, we may collect, retain and use any information that you provide. 

**Do we use "cookies" or "web beacons"?**

We do use "cookies" to collect Site usage data and to improve your experience on the Sites and our service generally. A “cookie” is a small data file transferred to your computer for access on future visits to the Site, which can tell us that you (or someone using the same computer or IP address) visited our Site(s) before, what clips you’ve listened to, etc. You can stop accepting cookies by setting your Internet browser accordingly, but this will likely result in our not recognizing you or your preferences on future visits, so you may have to re-enter certain information. 

The Sites and e-mails from us may contain electronic images known as "web beacons." These are files that allow us to count visitors to our Sites, to tell if an ad has been viewed or if an e-mail has been opened or forwarded, or to serve particular content or services. Web beacons collect limited non-personal information, including beacon number, time and date of a page or e-mail view, and a description of the page on which the web beacon resides, all of which we may store and use. Disabling cookies may prevent some beacons’ activity, but generally the beacons will operate if you visit the Sites or open e-mails from us. 

**What kind of "cookies" do we use?**

Based on the guidelines found in the ICC UK Cookie guide, we may use the following categories: 

**Strictly Necessary Cookies**

These cookies are essential in enabling you to browse our website and use its features. Without these cookies, services like shopping carts and electronic payments cannot be provided. For these types of cookies that are strictly required, no user consent is necessary. 

**Performance Cookies**

These cookies collect anonymous information on how visitors use our website and whether they encounter error messages from our web pages. All information gathered is aggregated and therefore anonymized. They are only used to improve how a website works. By using our website, you agree that we can place these types of cookies on your device. 

**Functionality Cookies**

These cookies allow our websites to remember choices you make while browsing, like language, font size, and user name preferences. We may also remember preferences such as text size, fonts and other customizable site elements. They may also be used to enable you to watch videos or comment on a blog. The information these cookies collect will not personally identify you, and they cannot track your browsing activity outside our websites. When you choose these preferences, you agree that we can place these functional customization cookies on your device. 

**Advertising Cookies**

These cookies are used to deliver targeted advertising as may be relevant to you and your interests. They are also used to limit the number of times you see an advertisement and help measure the effectiveness of the campaign. They remember you have visited a website and is shared with other sites such as advertisers. They may be linked to functionality provided by the other sites. You can choose whether to allow these cookies by changing your cookie settings in your browser.   
You can [opt-out here.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/)

**What do we do with the information we collect?**

Our main use for the personal information we collect is to process your registration, purchases and payments, and to maintain your account on an ongoing basis. If you are a content supplier, we will also use your personal information to make accountings and pay royalties to you. If you enter any contests, promotions, giveaways or other optional programs, we will use the information you provide to facilitate and communicate with you about that particular transaction, such as to notify you whether you’ve won, to deliver prizes. If you maintain a DJ profile page, we may use your personal information to communicate with you about that. 

We may also use your personal and non-personal information to enhance your experience with the Sites and our service, such as sending you e-mails and otherwise providing you with other information, content and material in which we think you may be interested; displaying content and ads according to your prior browsing history, preferences and location; fulfilling your orders; providing customer service and responding to your questions and comments; or contacting you about your account or about our and and partners’ promotions, contests, surveys, or other promotions. 

We may use information learned from cookies and web beacons to make sure that our content and emails are in a format that you can read, to analyze trends about which Sites, content and e-mails are popular and are being read and/or forwarded, to maintain a history of e-mail activity, and to evaluate the effectiveness and efficiency of certain communications. 

Your feedback and other information will also be used to evaluate and enhance our Sites and service. For example, we may analyze the traffic and usage of our Site; the participation rate of our various promotions, offerings, e-mails, and other programs; and the popularity of our content, artists, and participating suppliers. We may also use that information for product development purposes, such as determining what other labels, artists, products and services our users are interested in, and for technical purposes such as monitoring the functionality of our servers and e-mail systems. 

**Do we share the information we collect with third parties?**

We may share the information that we collect, both personal and non-personal, with third parties such as advertisers, contest sponsors, promotional and marketing partners, and the labels, artists and others who provide our content or whose products or services we think may interest you. We may also share it with our current and future affiliated companies and business partners, and if we are involved in a merger, asset sale or other business reorganization, we may also share or transfer your personal and non-personal information to our successors-in-interest. 

We may engage trusted third party service providers to perform functions and provide services to us, such as hosting and maintaining our servers and the Site, database storage and management, e-mail management, storage marketing, credit card processing, customer service and fulfilling orders for products and services you may purchase through the Site. We will likely share your personal information, and possibly some non-personal information, with these third parties to enable them to perform these services for us and for you. 

We may share portions of our log file data, including IP addresses, for analytics purposes with third parties such as web analytics partners, application developers, and ad networks. If your IP address is shared, it may be used to estimate general location and other technographics such as connection speed, whether you have visited the Sites in a shared location, and type of the device used to visit the Sites. They may aggregate information about our advertising and what you see on the Sites and then provide auditing, research and reporting for us and our advertisers. 

We may also disclose personal and non-personal information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate in order to respond to claims, legal process (including subpoenas), to protect our rights and interests or those of a third party, the safety of the public or any person, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity, or to otherwise comply with applicable court orders, laws, rules and regulations. 

**Is your information secure?**

We employ administrative, physical, and electronic measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access. All credit transactions occur in a secure area of the Site using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software to process orders, which encrypts the information you input on the Site. For the storage and processing of credit card information, we engage a third party certified as compliant with the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS). 

In addition, all personal user information is stored behind a firewall with limited administrative access. However, please be aware that despite our best efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. 

Any information or material you may enter in publicly viewable portion of the Sites, such as on a DJ profile page, an online forum or comment section, chat room, or bulletin board, will be readily accessible to the general public. Therefore, do not enter in those areas of the Site any personal information (e.g., your name, e-mail or postal address, credit card details) or other information or materials that you would not wish to be publicly available. This also applies to any communications you may have directly with other users of the Sites. 

**Does this Policy apply to any other sites or services?**

The Sites may contain links to the websites associated with record labels, DJs, artists, and suppliers of content to the Sites and to our advertisers, marketing partners, contest sponsors, or other third parties. Links, advertisements, promotions, or other mentions do not constitute our endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with any third party, or of their products or services. 

Third party sites have their own privacy and data protection policies and practices, and may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, and collect or solicit both personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information from you under rules different from this Policy. We do not control other sites, companies or persons and can’t be responsible for your experience once you leave our Sites. Therefore, we strongly encourage you to carefully read the privacy policies, terms of use and other policies of other sites you visit. 

**What is our policy regarding children's information?**

Our Sites, products and and services are not intended for, and we do not knowingly accept registration or collect personally identifiable information from, engage in financial transactions with, or otherwise transact with, children under 13 years old. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal identifiable Information, we will delete it from our files. If parents or legal guardians become aware that their under-13s have provided us with personally identifiable information without their consent (or that we have otherwise collected or obtained such information), they should contact us at contact@zippytune.com. 

If you are between the ages of 13 and 18, or otherwise below the age of legal majority where you live, you must obtain permission from your parent or legal guardian before registering with one or more of the Sites, using a credit card or providing any information about themselves to us or anyone else over the Internet. 

**Where do we store and use your information?**

We collect, store and process the information we collect in the United States of America. If you are outside the U.S., then your personal and non-personal information may be transferred to the U.S. 

California residents may request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes, and those who have an established business relationship with us may also choose to opt-out from such disclosures. To do so, please contact us by one of the methods described below stating your specific request and your name, address, e-mail address and phone number. This will not prohibit disclosure of information for non-marketing purposes. 

E-mails that you receive from us will include specific instructions on how to unsubscribe from receiving certain communications. You may also send an email to us at contact@zippytune.com to update or correct the personal information we have on file for you or to be unsubscribed from marketing or promotional e-mailings. 

As long as you remain a registered user of one or more of the Sites, or continue to make purchases or provide us with content, then we still reserve the right to contact you about your account and to inform you about operational matters regarding the Sites.
